<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<content id="ws_3487418410"
         name="Timelines Xenon F B and H"
         description="Timelines Xenon F B and H&#13;&#10;Require Timelines Official DLC&#13;&#10;Nexus link : https://www.nexusmods.com/x4foundations/mods/1709&#13;&#10;NB: Please note that the Workshop Mod could receive less regular updates than the Nexus Mod&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;fbhunlock&#13;&#10;Allow you to research F, B and H blueprints with a new build method once unlocked through Timelines and getting the ship in open universe.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;What it does ?&#13;&#10;Unlock research to be the same as for the Cutlass, Odachi or Sapporo, once unlocked in Timelines, get the ship in open universe and start the research to build them.&#13;&#10;To be reminder, the Cutlass, Odachi and Sapporo must be unlocked through Timelines or the Kaori Plot (Quettanauts).&#13;&#10;As for the 3 ships now buildable through this mod, you must also have done the Xenon Equipment research beforehand.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Walkthrough&#13;&#10;For the Xenon F (in no particular order) :&#13;&#10;- Do &quot;Impeded Extraction&quot; Nodus in Timelines (Rating 1)&#13;&#10;- Get a Xenon F (the one unlocked through Timelines in Nopileus' Fortune II or another)&#13;&#10;- Research &quot;Xenon Equipment&quot; (you must own a Xenon F after completing the research)&#13;&#10;NB : You must own a Xenon F at the time all the criteria are met&#13;&#10;THEN: The new F research should be available, research it and it will unlock the Xenon F to be build in your own Wharf&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;For the Xenon B (in no particular order) :&#13;&#10;- Do &quot;Attack on Antigone&quot; Nodus in Timelines (Rating 1)&#13;&#10;- Get a Xenon B (the one unlocked through Timelines in Antigone Memorial or another)&#13;&#10;- Research &quot;Xenon Equipment&quot; (you must own a Xenon B after completing the research)&#13;&#10;NB : You must own a Xenon B at the time all the criteria are met&#13;&#10;THEN: The new B research should be available, research it and it will unlock the Xenon B to be build in your own Wharf&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;For the Xenon H (in no particular order) :&#13;&#10;- Do &quot;The Fade&quot; Terminus in Timelines (Rating 1)&#13;&#10;- Get a Xenon H (the one unlocked through Timelines in Tharkra's Cascade XV or another)&#13;&#10;- Research &quot;Xenon Equipment&quot; (you must own a Xenon H after completing the research)&#13;&#10;NB : You must own a Xenon H at the time all the criteria are met&#13;&#10;THEN: The new H research should be available, research it and it will unlock the Xenon H to be build in your own Shipyard&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Technically (How it works) ?&#13;&#10;- CUE which enables F, B and H research is triggered with the same conditions which adds ships in the universe from Vanilla Timelines&#13;&#10;- If you met Timelines requirement, have researched Xenon Equipment and own a F, B or H, additionals research for the designated ship will be available for research&#13;&#10;- Once the research is done, you will be able to build the designated ship with a new Default method or Terran method. The old Default method has become Xenon method and is still not available to the player.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Alternative ?&#13;&#10;This mod aim to add these 3 ships build method in a &quot;lore friendly&quot; way, reproducing the way the Cutlass, Odachi and Sapporo are made available for building, but with the Xenon Reseach Equipment in addition.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;If you want a more &quot;straight foward&quot; method to get these ships for building, you can look for Xenon Ship Research (which can also let you play AS Xenon/Yaki).&#13;&#10;Xenon Ship Research is incompatible with mine since they does almost the same thing, but in a different way. I looked the cue made by TheShooter36, and they are not alike mine, since the doesnt introduce a new building method but instead change the Xenon method to be accessible to player.&#13;&#10;Also, he doesnt rely on Timelines to add the ship building. TLDR; Some features of his mod are in conflict with mines, even if they are not done the same: Incompatible.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;There is also Xenon unlocked blueprints by research (M0 playable) and Terran ships which I didnt inspect to see how it's done.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Install&#13;&#10;Regular install through Vortex or manually. Save game compatible. But make a backup, we never know, if the mod isn't your taste.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Uninstall&#13;&#10;Shouldn't be a BIG problem. Ships already built will remain, but you won't be able to rebuild them. Since the Vanilla Xenon Equipment research will still allow you to change equipment, your will still be able to change ship loadout.&#13;&#10;BUT&#13;&#10;You might encounter problems in the research menu, as some entries will disappear.&#13;&#10;If you want to keep you save game clean I wouldn't recommend to uninstall the mod.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Requirements ?&#13;&#10;- Timelines DLC&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Redistribution and modification&#13;&#10;BSD 2-Clause License&#13;&#10;Copyright (c) 2025, laryakan&#13;&#10;You are free to use, modify and redistribute any code or assets of mine&#13;&#10;which is not directly extracted from the game as soon as you mention the&#13;&#10;above Copyright.&#13;&#10;A link to my github is provided below. A little mention is all I ask.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;- github : https://github.com/laryakan/fbhunlock&#13;&#10;- nexus : https://www.nexusmods.com/x4foundations/mods/1709&#13;&#10;- nexus user : https://next.nexusmods.com/profile/Laryakan"
         author="Laryakan"
         version="102"
         date="2025-05-28"
         save="false"
         lastupdate="1748169970">
	<dependency id="ego_dlc_timelines"
	            optional="false"
	            name="Timelines"/>
</content>
